TALINE AINEIN



PROFILE

Fourth year commerce student with experience in leadership and building relationships with future clients. Strengths in sales, customer service, time management, and interpersonal skills. Independent, reliable, quick learner, determined, and competitive. Interested in pursuing a future in Consulting. Fluent in English and Arabic; working knowledge in French.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Commerce Completion: Dec 2015

Sauder School of Business, University of British Columbia, Vancouver, BC

- Double Major in Finance and HR
- Dean's Honour Roll Standing: 83% Third year (first term) average
- Relevant Courses: Corporate Finance (85% final), Investment Theory (88% final), Introduction to Finance (80% final), Managerial Accounting (80% final), HR (84% final)
- Direct Entry Status one of 6% of over 6000 applicants granted direct entry into Sauder
- Exchange to Chulalongkorn University (Bangkok, Thailand) 2014W

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Service Representative

May 2013-Present

Scotiabank Yaletown, Vancouver, BC

- Increased efficiency and performance of the Financial Advisor and Personal Banking Officer by booking appointments with appropriate clients
- Exceeded monthly sales goals by recognizing client opportunities to invest and borrow
- Collaborated with the Financial Advisor to secure a quality referral for a \$350,000 mortgage

Blackberry Promotional Representative

May 2013-Aug 2013

Ncompass International, Vancouver, BC

• Enhanced awareness and recognition of the new Blackberry Z10 by 20% by proactively approaching and clearly communicating product benefits and features to over 3000 potential consumers in high traffic areas around Vancouver and at the Alicia Keys Concert

Marketing Director Intern

Apr 2012-Sep 2012

TriGrid, Vancouver, BC

- As a team, increased sales by 40% through developing and implementing social media and visual print ad campaigns
- Generated a pool of 56 applicants through the use of strong interpersonal skills, resulting in the recruitment of 11 UBC Brand Ambassador candidates

Sales Associate Sep 2009-Aug 2011

American Eagle, Vancouver, BC

- Consistently exceeded individual sale goals by up to 10% by asking appropriate questions to assess customer needs and making recommendations of suitable products
- Increased online sales and customer satisfaction by suggesting alternative products not available in retail locations

COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT

Volunteer Sep 2014-Present

BC Children's Hospital, Vancouver, BC

• Facilitating activities and providing support to families at various clinics in the hospital

Mentor Sep 2008-Sep 2014

Big Brothers Big Sisters, Vancouver, BC

- Awarded Mentor of the Year 2011 by demonstrating extreme commitment and dedication to mentoring young children
- Raised over \$1024 by contacting personal networks and soliciting donations within the community in a span of 2 weeks

INTERESTS

Snowboarding, skydiving, experiencing new cultures through international travel, horseback riding